collagevideo.com 2017-01-25

# Privacy Statement – Collage Video

## Privacy Statement for Collage Video

Collage Video has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the Web site www.collagevideo.com. 

 **Security**  This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control: All transactions which involve credit card information are carried out using a secure server. 

 **Order form information**  We collect contact information (postal address, email address and phone number) and financial information (credit card numbers). 

 **Contact information**  is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary, and to deliver products and services. The customer's phone number will only be used if there are problems with an order. Collage Video does not solicit orders by telephone, or share customer phone numbers with others. 

The customer's email address is used if there are problems with an order. Collage Video may also use this address to send our Monthly Newsletter. However, you can easily opt out of that service when you place your order or in the "opt out" section of the Newsletter. Collage Video does NOT share email addresses with others. 

The customer's postal address will be used for deliveries, and for credit card approval. Collage Video will also use postal address for mailing our catalog to customers and those who request it. The postal address may also be used to share with other companies who may want to contact our visitors by postal mail. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products purchased. Collage Video does not share this information with others. 

 **Public forums**  This site makes forums and reviews by users available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Please be careful when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

 **Choice/Opt-out**  Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us . 

You can send email to collage@collagevideo.com 

You can send mail to the following postal address:   
Collage Video   
210 West Parkway, Suite 7  
Pompton Plains, NJ 07444. 

You can call the following telephone number: 1-800-433-6769. Outside the US and Canada, you can call 201-464-4921. 

 **Cookies**  Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart if you leave our site and return. Our shopping cart system should work even if you have cookies turned off. But if you leave the site and return later, you are less likely to find your shopping cart if you do not accept cookies. In addition, third party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites on the internet. These vendors uses cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. Users may opt out of vendors' use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page:[http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

 **Information automatically logged**  Our web server (like nearly all web servers) logs your IP address, used to identify your computer on the internet. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. We keep statistics on the number of visitors to our site, but we do not track individual users by IP address. We do not share this information with others. 

 **Contacting the web site**  If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [collage@collagevideo.com](mailto:collage@collagevideo.com)
